

KATIE FULLMER designer & developer



ABOUT

I have worked in the web design and development space for over a decade, and have continually broadened my skillsets over that time. My specialty is designing and developing custom websites and applications, utilizing a wide range of technologies while delivering custom interfaces that focus on user experience, performance, and functionality. I also have extensive experience in designing ads for print and online use.

This industry is constantly evolving, so I make it a priority to stay at the forefront of the web technology and standards. One of my favorite aspects of web design and development is the opportunity for creative problem-solving—I love taking on new challenges with each project and seeing the end result come to fruition. I am always eager to learn new skills, and am open to new opportunities and experiences.



CONTACT

www.katiefullmer.com



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS / AUG 2008 - MAY 2012

College of Art & Design - Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana

ART HISTORY MINOR DEGREE / AUG 2008 - MAY 2012

College of Art & Design - Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana



EXPERIENCE

HEALTH CONNECTIVE / JUN 2012 - PRESENT

Senior Designer & Front End Developer in New Orleans, LA Provide custom web design and application development, as well as online and print advertising for clients.

BEACHVIEW ENERGY / AUG 2017 - FEB 2020

Freelance Graphic Designer in Brunswick, GA

Provide quarterly customer newsletter layout and design, branding and promotional design services.

UTILITY SERVICES - POWER SECURE / JUL 2012 - AUG 2018

Freelance Graphic Designer in Atlanta, GA

Design the company-wide, quaterly newsletter along with a monthly newsletter for the Utility Services division along with other promtional materials.

AMERICAN ALL STAR / MAY 2008 - MAY 2017

Freelance Designer, Camp Director & Dance Instructor in Mandeville, LA Design all promotional media such as brochures, t-shirts, informational binders, & folders.

DIG MAGAZINE / AUG 2011 - JUN 2012

Graphic Designer in Baton Rouge, LA

Design various medias on strict deadlines such as advertisements, posters, media kits, identities, & layouts.

LSU ITS / JAN 2009 - AUG 2011

Information Technology Services Student Worker in Baton Rouge, LA



AFFILIATIONS

AIGA / 2011 - PRESENT Professional Association for Design

DELTA DELTA / 2009 - 2012

Order of Omega

GDSA / 2009 - 2012

LSU Graphic Design Student Association